theyoump3.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy - TheYouMp3

### TheYouMp3 Privacy Policy 

We, TheYouMp3, know that protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.theyoump3.com and TheYouMp3 and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to TheYouMp3 include www.theyoump3.com. By using TheYouMp3 website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

#### Collection of your Personal Information

TheYouMp3 may collect personally identifiable information such as your name. If you purchase TheYouMp3’ products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. TheYouMp3 may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, household income, political affiliation, race and religion. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by TheYouMp3. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of TheYouMp3 website. 

TheYouMp3 encourages you to review the privacy statements of the websites you choose to link to from TheYouMp3 is not responsible for the privacy statements of other content on websites outside of TheYouMp3 website.

#### Use of your Personal Information

TheYouMp3 collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

TheYouMp3 may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services from TheYouMp3 and its affiliates, TheYouMp3 may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

TheYouMp3 does not sell, rent, lease its customer lists to third parties.

TheYouMp3 may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries.

TheYouMp3 may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within TheYouMp3, in order to determine what TheYouMp3 services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within TheYouMp3 to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in particular subject area.

TheYouMp3 will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conformed to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TheYouMp3 or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TheYouMp3; and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TheYouMp3, or the public.

#### Use of Cookies

TheYouMp3 website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or to deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and only be read by a web server in the domain that used the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize TheYouMp3 pages, or register with TheYouMp3 site or services, or cookie helps TheYouMp3 to recall your specific information on subsequent visits, this simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same TheYouMp3 website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use TheYouMp3 features that you customized.

Cookies maybe stored by third parties such as Google or DoubleClick, via third party content displayed on our website such as advertisments etc. By using our service, you consent to the use by these third parties of your personal information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of TheYouMp3 services or websites you visit.

#### Children Under Thirteen

TheYouMp3 does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from TheYouMp3 by contacting us here:

Website:  www.theyoump3.com

#### Changes to this Statement

TheYouMp3 will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. TheYouMp3 encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how TheYouMp3 is protecting your information.

#### Contact Information

TheYouMp3 welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that TheYouMp3 has not adhered to this Statement, please contact TheYouMp3 at: 

TheYouMp3   
Website:  www.theyoump3.com   
Email: webmaster@theyoump3.com 

Effective as of August 05, 2014
